非常棒  我们的手机已经可以正常接收数据了
Great work. Thumbs up. The data has landed safely on
但我又想了想
our phones. But I was thinking about it, and actually
我们定义一个固定的邮编（去获取天气数据）
instead of hard coding our post code in, we'd really
这对于用户来说肯定是不行的
[SOUND] like our sun train app user, to be able
他们应该可以在设置里自定义位置信息
to change their location in the settings. So let's make
那我们就多加上一个邮编的参数  让我们这个类变得更贴心吧
the FetchWeatherTask more flexible by having it take as input
鉴于我们要这么做  我们应该
a postal code parameter. While we're doing that, we should
通过这个机会给项目做一些重构
also take this opportunity to do a little bit of refactoring.
之前是通过字符串拼接  得到的服务器请求URL
Instead of concatenating the strings for the server query
取而代之的是UriBuilder这个类来组装这个URL
URL, we should use a UriBuilder Class to build
我们可以定义一个基础的 URL 地址
up he URL. We can declare a base URL
然后把每个参数拼接组装上去
and then append each pair of query PARAM and
这些参数包括邮编信息
PARAM values onto it. This includes PARAM's for post
输出JSON数据格式、使用公制单位以及天数
code. JSON format, metric units, and date count. This'll
未来我们允许用户自己设置这些信息
make it easier in the future if we ever
我们代码实现起来就会很简单了
have to make these options configurable by the user.
如果你想确认拼接之后的URL地址是正确的  做完这些之后
If you want to verify that the URL is built up properly. After
你可以把这个地址打印在日志监控器里
you do these tasks, you can use verbose logging to print it out.